





### **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Last Active: 21-Jan-21

Marital Status: Married

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Jump to Section Work Experience | Ec

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

#### Summary

IT Project Manager having overall 15+ years of experience.

5+ years of experience in multimillion engagement with focus on Project Management, Service delivery Management, Transition & Transformation Management, Customer Management, Automation and Continuous improvements. Planning, maintaining delivery parameters like resourcing to have optimal cost of delivery, internal stakeholder and financial management meeting organization goals.

Key Skills: Project Manager, Project Management, Software Development, Application Programming, Service Management, Customer Management, Continuous Improvement, Agile Methodology, Digital Transformation

## **Work Experience**

Wipro Limited as Project Manager

May 2010 to Till Date

Project Manager managing multiple agile scrum projects under M2O Digital.

Executive briefing and reporting on scrum metrics, project progress, risks during weekly portfolio review with senior delivery management and provide updates to internal and external stakeholders.

Managed Digital Transformation for multiple programs bringing improvements in terms of quality of deliverables, increased release frequency enabling faster time to market.

Executing and delivering Q&R validation projects (Software Validation, Infra Qualification and Data Migration) by collaboratively working with IT delivery, business, SaaS suppliers, Q&R involving SQA, VE, BPO, BPE, IT BA, TL's for all releases.

Experience in executing migration projects.

Implementing DevOps methodologies in terms of people, process and engineering capabilities to increase agility.

Managing projects and support engagement in multiple technology skills - AEM, ADAM, STEP, Eloqua Marketing Cloud, Janrain, MS.Net, Java, XSLT

Tower Lead, Service Lead, and Incident Manager managing Digital Operations.

Transition Lead during AMS engagement consolidation under Digital Operations.

Release Management.

Major incident & crisis management, Change Management, Problem Management.

Driving & Implementation of lean methodologies, CSI's delivering tangible benefits to delivery and customers.

Experience in nurturing a strong work force who are T-Shaped engineers and full stack developers.

Wipro Limited as Project Manager

May 2010 to May 2010

Project Manager - Infopark, Cochin, India (Sep 2020 onwards)

o Project Manager - High Tech Campus, Eindhoven, Netherlands (Feb 2019 - Aug 2020)

o Project Manager - Infopark, Cochin, India (May 2017 - Jan 2019)

o Service Lead, Tower Lead - Infopark, Cochin, India (Jan 2014 - Apr 2017)

o Incident Manager - Infopark, Cochin, India (Mar 2013 - Dec 2013)

o Test Lead - Infopark, Cochin, India (May 2010 - Feb 2013)

Hughes Systique Ltd as Sr. Test Engineer

Jul 2007 to Apr 2010

Wipro Limited as Software Engineer Jul 2005 to Jun 2007

^ Back to Top

#### **Education**

PG: MCA (Computers) from Vellore Institute of Technology (VIT) in 2005

^ Back to Top

### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PROJECT MANAGEMENT		0	0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

### Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak	
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓	
Malayalam	Expert	✓	✓	✓	
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓	

^ Back to Top

#### **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: **General**Physically Challenged: **No** 

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.